[**Generate Your First Deal 🏠 Conquer Cold Calling in 4 Weeks!**
----------------------------------------------------------------

Cold Calling Challenge! Free to Register!

**Learn More** _keyboard\_arrow\_right_](https://www.dealmachine.com/cold-calling-challenge?hsLang=en)

_star_ _star_ _star_ _star_ _star_

4.8 out of 5 stars in over 5,000 reviews

**Our Promise**
---------------

Privacy is important to your success and your trust is crucial to our business.

By using DealMachine, we promise to clearly inform you about how your data will be used and protected. Our [terms of service](https://www.dealmachine.com/terms-of-service?hsLang=en) covers your use and access to our services. Here's our privacy policy:

We collect your basic contact information including your **name** and **email** to maintain your DealMachine account.

We collect your **phone number** and **address** so that you may send mail through DealMachine. Your address and phone number are used as your outgoing mail return address.

We collect the **property addresses** you're interested in so that we can look up the property owner and send mail on your behalf. This is a particularly important area of privacy to many of our customers. You own the property address data and we promise:

* We never use your property address list or corresponding owner list to send mail from us
* We won't share your data with others
* You may export your data from the app

**Our Privacy Policy**
----------------------

**Our Promise**

Privacy is important to your success and your trust is crucial to our business.

By using DealMachine, we promise to clearly inform you about how your data will be used and protected.

We collect your basic contact information including your name and email to maintain your DealMachine account.

We collect your phone number and address so that you may send mail through DealMachine. Your address and phone number are used as your outgoing mail return address.

We collect the property addresses you're interested in so that we can look up the property owner and send mail on your behalf. This is a particularly important area of privacy to many of our customers. You own the property address data and we promise:

We never use your property address list or corresponding owner list to send mail from us We won't share your property address data with others We won’t sell your property address data You may export your property address data from the app

**Our Privacy Policy** **(Effective Date: March 1, 2020)** This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes how DealMachine L.L.C. (“Company,” “we,” “our,” or “us) collects, uses, and shares personal information of users that interact with Company through the DealMachine application (the “App) and its corresponding website [http://www.dealmachine.com/](https://www.dealmachine.com/home?hsLang=en) (the “Site”). Collectively, the App and Site will hereinafter be referred to as “DealMachine.” We will also outline the controls and choices you have about when and how you choose to share your personal data.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

* We may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Policy periodically. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to alert you when material changes have been made to this Policy by email as well as prominent disclosure in DealMachine.
* Your continued use of DealMachine following such notice constitutes your consent to any changes in the Policy as in effect on the date of such use.

**Data Collected**

We collect information from and about users of DealMachine: directly from you when you provide it to us, and automatically when you use the App. When you interact with DealMachine, we collect two types of information: Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“NPII”). Personal data is defined as: “Any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('data subject'); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.” Company complies with its data protection obligations by keeping personal data up to date; by storing and destroying it securely; by not collecting or retaining excessive amounts of data; by protecting personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access and disclosure and by ensuring that appropriate technical measures are in place to protect personal data. When you download, register with, or use DealMachine, we may ask you to provide certain PII, which may include your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number. WE WILL NOT REQUEST YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER AND YOU SHOULD NEVER PROVIDE IT IN DEALMACHINE. When creating a user account, we may ask users to create a username, password and to choose their time zone preferences. When registering for a paid account or making purchases through DealMachine, we may ask users to also provide their name, mailing address, billing address, email address, telephone number, credit card number, and CVV. We do not store your credit card data on any of our servers and are fully PCI compliant. You may also provide information for publication or display, such as customer testimonials and product reviews, where you may post information in public areas of DealMachine (“User Contributions”). User Contributions are posted and transmitted to others at your own risk. You consent to DealMachine’s use of User Contributions. Through the “Contact Us” (or similarly named) form and customer care channels (such as live chat), we may ask users to share information about their devices, platforms, internet connection, device settings, plug-ins, and other items for troubleshooting incoming inquiries. We also collect some information automatically when you visit DealMachine. This includes IP address and other online identifiers. We also record the pages that you visit, products you interacted with and other information about your activity on DealMachine. Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“NPII”) data, such as unique device identifier, referrer URL, location and time zone may be collected by Company so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.

**Our Use of Your Data and Our Legal Basis for Processing Your Data**

Company may use your personal information for our legitimate interests to: Provide you with DealMachine content, and any other information, products or services that you request from us; Send you emails, chats, or push notifications to otherwise respond to questions, concerns and customer support inquiries; Enable us to process orders for products and services from DealMachine; Send email confirmations, receipts and other transactional emails related to orders from DealMachine; Provide you with continuing access to your customer account in DealMachine, including your order history and access to digital products, event passes and subscription services; Administer membership records; Contact you (when necessary) in relation to orders; Maintain our own accounts and records; Create demographic automatic decision-making profiles for our subscribers, members, and visitors to target our email alerts, website marketing, push notifications, banners, special offers; Personalize your experience using automated decision-making for products, services, personalized content, recommendations, and features; Improve the services we offer you, or the functionality of DealMachine and ensure technical functionality of the same; Process your payment; Prevent or detect fraud; and To comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety of the Company. We also use information about you with your consent including to: Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions you have entered; Develop and display content, features and advertising tailored to your interests; Send marketing communications through subscribed channels about news, products, offers and events; and Fulfill any other purpose disclosed to you with your consent. We may use NPII (including information that has been de-identified) without obligation to you except as prohibited by applicable law. For information on your rights and choices regarding how we use your information, please see para. 7) (“Your Rights & Controlling Use of Your Data”).

**Payment Data**

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. We may share your information with third parties (e.g. an App Store like Apple, Inc. or Google LLC) for services such as payment processing, in which case the third party provider may store your payment processing data. We do not store credit card details or other financial information. Any purchases you make through the Apple App Store will also be governed by Apple’s privacy policy which is available here: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/) ; and any purchases you make through the Google Play Store will also be governed by Google’s terms, which are available here: [https://play.google.com/intl/ALL\_us/about/play-terms/index.html](https://play.google.com/intl/ALL_us/about/play-terms/index.html). If you sign up for a membership, payment plan or purchase any of our paid subscription services, your credit or debit card information (such as your name, address, card type, card number, CVV and expiration date) and other financial data that we need to process your payment may be collected and stored by the payment processors with which we work. We may also collect some limited information, such as your postal code, mobile number, and details of your transaction history, all of which are necessary to provide the services. In addition, the payment processors generally provide us with some limited information related to you, such as a unique token that enables you to make additional purchases using the information they’ve stored, and your card’s type, expiration date, and certain digits of your card number.

**Data Retention**

We keep your personal data for no longer than reasonably necessary. Company will retain purchase accounting records, tax, VAT and GST records for a minimum of 6 years as required by law. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Our data retention for physical product orders will not extend beyond 10 years, at which time your purchase data will be marked for permanent deletion and will no longer be accessible. If you purchase a digital product, you will be asked to create a username and password to log into your customer account portal in order to access the product(s) purchased. Digital product purchases grant ownership for a certain period of time (specified in the license) and data will be retained in order to carry out the stated guarantee. If your digital product is not accessed within a 6-year period at any point in time, your account will be deemed inactive. All inactive data will not be retained beyond 10 years at which time the data will be marked for permanent deletion. When you register to receive emails from Company, your personal data is stored so that we can continue to send you relevant emails. You may request removal at any time by notifying us as set forth in sec. 15) (Contact Us). Company retains non-personally identified data, including encrypted, anonymized and pseudonymized data for 10 years.

**Third Party Services, Websites and Information Collection**

Company may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with certain processes necessary for the operation of DealMachine. The data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that we request. If you register for DealMachine with a promo code from a DealMachine affiliate partner, we will share your name and email address with the affiliate partner for tracking purposes. DealMachine may include social media features such as links to our Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, SoundCloud, Vimeo and Twitter pages. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook. Company may, from time to time, provide links to third-party websites. We have no control over such websites and are not responsible for the content of these websites. This Privacy Policy does not extend to your use of such websites. You are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them. When you use DealMachine or its content, certain third parties may use automatic information collection technologies to collect information about you or your device. These third parties may include: Advertisers, ad networks, and ad servers. Your mobile device manufacturer. Your mobile service provider. These third parties may use tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Company. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites, apps, and other online services websites. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work). You can opt out of targeted advertising by: FACEBOOK - [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads) GOOGLE - [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous) BING - [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads) Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

**Your Rights & Controlling Use of Your Data**

You have several rights connected to the provision of your personal information to us from using DealMachine. Unless subject to an exemption, you have the following rights with respect to your personal data: The right to be provided with clear, transparent, and easily understandable information about how we use information and your rights regarding such information. The right to request a copy of your personal data which Company holds about you. The right to request that Company corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date. The right to request your personal data is erased under certain circumstances where there is no compelling reason for us to keep using it. There are exceptions to the erasure right. The right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time. The right to request that Company provide you with your personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller (where applicable). The right to “block” or suppress further use of your personal information. When processing is restricted, we can still store your information but may not be able to process it further. We maintain lists of people who have asked for further use of their personal information to be “blocked” to make sure the restriction is respected in the future. The right to object to certain types of personal data processing, including processing for direct marketing initiatives. If you have given your consent to anything we do with your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note that if you do withdraw your consent, it does not mean that anything we have done with your personal data with your consent up to that point is unlawful. You have the right to be promptly informed by us of any personal data loss, theft or compromise arising directly or indirectly from DealMachine. As permitted by law, we may charge a reasonable fee to cover our costs for responding to information requests and may require you to prove your identity. Following a request, we will use reasonable efforts to supply, correct or delete personal information about you in our files. To exercise all relevant rights and for queries or complaints, please contact us as set forth in sec. 15) (“Contact Us”).

**Information Collection & Tracking Technologies**

To enhance your experience with DealMachine, we may use “cookies.” Cookies are small text files we place on your computer or device that can store information such as your preferences. We may also use “log files” to track actions occurring on DealMachine and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. **Web Beacons.** Pages of DealMachine and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages, or opened an email, and for other related DealMachine statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain content and verifying system and server integrity). Please note that we do not alter DealMachine’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your internet browser.

**Data Security**

We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure data collected by DealMachine. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. It is recommended your password use both upper-case and lower-case letters, include one or more numerical digits, and include special characters in accordance with generally accepted password strength recommendations. It is recommended that you ensure that your internet browser is up to date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings. While the Company is committed to protection of your information, the transmission of information over the internet is done at your own risk and we cannot ensure the security of your data transmitted to DealMachine.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of DealMachine that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us as set forth in sec. 15) (“Contact Us”). [View the full California Policy here](https://www.dealmachine.com/california-privacy-policy?hsLang=en)

**Sale of Our Corporation**

As in any business venture, the sale, merger or declaration of bankruptcy of the company is always a possibility. Should the Company ever declare bankruptcy or should it or its assets ever be acquired by or merged into another organization, all customer information we have collected will be treated as an asset and may be transferred to a third party.

**Children’s Privacy**

DealMachine is not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information submitted by visitors to DealMachine who are under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and believe we have collected such information in a manner not permitted by the U.S. Children’s Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), please contact us as set forth in sec. 15) (“Contact Us”), and we will remove such data to the extent required by COPPA.

**International Transfer**

We are based in the United States. and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. If you are accessing DealMachine from outside of the U.S., please be aware that information collected through DealMachine may be transferred to, processed, stored, and used in the U.S. and other jurisdictions. Data protection laws in the U.S. and other jurisdictions may be different from those of your country of residence. Your use of DealMachine or provision of any information therefore constitutes your consent to the transfer to and from, processing, usage, sharing, and storage of your information in the U.S.

**General**

If any court or competent authority finds that any provision of this Privacy Policy (or part of any provision) is invalid, illegal, or unenforceable, that provision or part-provision will, to the extent required, be deleted, and the validity and enforceability of the other provisions of this Privacy Policy will not be affected. Unless otherwise agreed, no delay, act or omission by a party in exercising any right or remedy will be deemed a waiver of that, or any other right or remedy. **Contact Us.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the data practices of DealMachine, or your dealings with DealMachine, please contact us: By email to support@dealmachine.com.

@ 2023 DealMachine L.L.C. [Privacy Policy](https://www.dealmachine.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en) [Terms of Service](https://www.dealmachine.com/terms-of-service?hsLang=en)

801 Shelby St, Indianapolis, IN 46203

.svg)
